[
  {
    "id": "user-001-test-master-0",
    "userId": "user-001-test",
    "front": "Hello",
    "back": "Olá",
    "createdAt": "2025-12-19T20:00:34.582Z",
    "updatedAt": "2025-12-19T20:07:34.658Z",
    "lastReviewDate": "2025-12-19T20:07:34.656Z",
    "nextReviewDate": "2025-12-21T20:07:34.654Z",
    "interval": 2,
    "repetitionCount": 1,
    "easeFactor": 2.6
  },
  {
    "id": "user-001-test-master-1",
    "userId": "user-001-test",
    "front": "Thank you",
    "back": "Obrigado / Obrigada",
    "createdAt": "2025-12-19T20:00:34.582Z",
    "updatedAt": "2025-12-19T20:07:36.386Z",
    "lastReviewDate": "2025-12-19T20:07:36.384Z",
    "nextReviewDate": "2025-12-21T20:07:36.384Z",
    "interval": 2,
    "repetitionCount": 1,
    "easeFactor": 2.6
  },
  {
    "id": "user-001-test-master-2",
    "userId": "user-001-test",
    "front": "Please",
    "back": "Por favor",
    "createdAt": "2025-12-19T20:00:34.582Z",
    "updatedAt": "2025-12-19T20:07:37.806Z",
    "lastReviewDate": "2025-12-19T20:07:37.805Z",
    "nextReviewDate": "2025-12-21T20:07:37.805Z",
    "interval": 2,
    "repetitionCount": 1,
    "easeFactor": 2.6
  },
  {
    "id": "user-001-test-master-3",
    "userId": "user-001-test",
    "front": "Good morning",
    "back": "Bom dia",
    "createdAt": "2025-12-19T20:00:34.582Z",
    "updatedAt": "2025-12-19T20:07:53.095Z",
    "lastReviewDate": "2025-12-19T20:07:53.092Z",
    "nextReviewDate": "2025-12-21T20:07:53.092Z",
    "interval": 2,
    "repetitionCount": 1,
    "easeFactor": 1.4000000000000001
  },
  {
    "id": "user-001-test-master-4",
    "userId": "user-001-test",
    "front": "Good night",
    "back": "Boa noite",
    "createdAt": "2025-12-19T20:00:34.582Z",
    "updatedAt": "2025-12-19T20:07:51.598Z",
    "lastReviewDate": "2025-12-19T20:07:51.597Z",
    "nextReviewDate": "2025-12-21T20:07:51.596Z",
    "interval": 2,
    "repetitionCount": 1,
    "easeFactor": 1.4000000000000001
  },
  {
    "id": "user-001-test-master-5",
    "userId": "user-001-test",
    "front": "Yes",
    "back": "Sim",
    "createdAt": "2025-12-19T20:00:34.582Z",
    "updatedAt": "2025-12-19T20:07:52.564Z",
    "lastReviewDate": "2025-12-19T20:07:52.562Z",
    "nextReviewDate": "2025-12-21T20:07:52.562Z",
    "interval": 2,
    "repetitionCount": 1,
    "easeFactor": 1.4000000000000001
  },
  {
    "id": "user-001-test-master-6",
    "userId": "user-001-test",
    "front": "No",
    "back": "Não",
    "createdAt": "2025-12-19T20:00:34.582Z",
    "updatedAt": "2025-12-19T20:07:53.605Z",
    "lastReviewDate": "2025-12-19T20:07:53.604Z",
    "nextReviewDate": "2025-12-21T20:07:53.604Z",
    "interval": 2,
    "repetitionCount": 1,
    "easeFactor": 1.4000000000000001
  },
  {
    "id": "user-001-test-master-7",
    "userId": "user-001-test",
    "front": "Excuse me",
    "back": "Com licença",
    "createdAt": "2025-12-19T20:00:34.582Z",
    "updatedAt": "2025-12-19T20:07:54.240Z",
    "lastReviewDate": "2025-12-19T20:07:54.238Z",
    "nextReviewDate": "2025-12-21T20:07:54.238Z",
    "interval": 2,
    "repetitionCount": 1,
    "easeFactor": 2.2800000000000002
  },
  {
    "id": "user-001-test-master-8",
    "userId": "user-001-test",
    "front": "Where is the bathroom?",
    "back": "Onde é o banheiro?",
    "createdAt": "2025-12-19T20:00:34.582Z",
    "updatedAt": "2025-12-19T20:07:55.045Z",
    "lastReviewDate": "2025-12-19T20:07:55.044Z",
    "nextReviewDate": "2025-12-20T20:07:55.044Z",
    "interval": 1,
    "repetitionCount": 1,
    "easeFactor": 2.02
  },
  {
    "id": "user-001-test-master-9",
    "userId": "user-001-test",
    "front": "I need help",
    "back": "Eu preciso de ajuda",
    "createdAt": "2025-12-19T20:00:34.582Z",
    "updatedAt": "2025-12-19T20:07:55.479Z",
    "lastReviewDate": "2025-12-19T20:07:55.477Z",
    "nextReviewDate": "2025-12-20T20:07:55.477Z",
    "interval": 1,
    "repetitionCount": 1,
    "easeFactor": 2.02
  }
]